《诉讼双雄》前情提要
Previously on Suits
我签了这个  贿赂指控就没了吗
So I sign this, and the bribery allegations are gone?
也没人会知道
And no one ever knows a thing.
你从没让我说明钱是做什么的
you never let me tell you what the money was for.
你没听懂  我说过我不在乎
You didn't listen to me when I told you I don't care.
那你在乎迈克盘问我之后
Well, do you care that after Mike grilled me,
我对他印象深刻
I was so impressed with him
好奇我为什么会忘记他吗
that I wonder why I'd forgotten him.
但找不到任何关于他
but I couldn't find any record of him
听我课的记录
ever being in my class.
就像他们也不会找到任何
Just like they're not gonna find any record
关于你收学生贿赂的记录一样
of you accepting a bribe from a student.
杰西卡
Jessica,
我会帮你保密
your secret is safe with me.
我告诉他你发现了
I told him you found out
我隐瞒了丹尼尔·哈德曼挪用公款的事
that I covered up Daniel Hardman's embezzlement
然后你现在想让我保守你的另一个秘密
And now you want me to protect another one of your secrets.
是同一个的秘密  路易
It's the same secret, Louis,
而且你在其中牵扯深度跟我一样
and you have just as much invested in it as I do.
你还想让我祝贺你上位[吻你戒指]  路易
You want me to kiss the ring, Louis,
在你做了那些事情之后
after what you did?
说得对  我做了
You're damn right I do,
因为我不在乎上位的手段
because I don't care how it got up there.
我的名字现在在墙上
My name is on that wall.
无论你喜欢与否
whether you like it or not.
你觉得这条领带如何
What do you think of this tie?
我觉得
I think...
我想用它把你绑起来
I want to tie you up with it.
是吗  这是哪来的兴致
Really? And what brought that on?
不知道  我觉得自己很强势
I don't know. I'm feeling powerful.
好吧
Okay, well,
那我们就
then let's make
来  实现  它
that happen.
等等
Wait.
你这是为了跟我缠绵
Is this to do things to me
还是为了拿到遥控器
or just to get control of the remote?
为什么不能两者都有呢
Why can't it be both?
瑞秋  如果你觉得我会让你看着《权力的游戏》
Rachel, if you think I'm gonna let you watch Game of Thrones
还在床上控制着我
while sexually dominating me,
那你就想对了
then you are absolutely right.
说真的  你怎么兴致这么高昂
Seriously, what's got you feeling so good?
就是觉得如释重负
Oh, it just feels like such a weight off
因为路易已经不...
now that Louis doesn't--
鄙视我了
Despise me?
知道还怎么样能有种如释重负之感吗
Ah, you know what else would feel like a weight off?
别别别
No. No, no, no.
从没人打固话找我的  除了我父母
Nobody ever calls the landline except my parents.
-如果出事了呢  -没事的
- What if something's wrong? - It's fine.
迈克
Mike.
好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
喂
Hello.
对  是我
Yeah, this is him.
嗯  我当然可以去见您
Yeah, of course I can come meet you.
能问问是什么事...喂
Can I ask what this is-- hello?
是谁
Who was it?
吉拉德教授
Professor Gerard.
他要我去见他
He wants me to go meet him.
他说是什么事了吗
Did he say what it was about?
没有  他挂断了
No, he hung up.
他要你什么时候去见他
When does he want you to meet him?
就现在
Right now.
-吉拉德教授  -谢谢你前来
- Professor Gerard. - Thanks for coming.
如果不是要事我也不会打扰你
I wouldn't have bothered you if it wasn't important.
没事  有什么能帮您的
It's not a problem. What can I help you with?
不是我
It's not me.
自由铁路公司的一名前雇员找到了我
A former employee at Liberty Rail reached out to me.
他称自己因知道事故真实原因而被解雇
He claims he was fired because he knows the real reason for the crash.
真实原因是什么
And what was the real reason?
他不肯说
He wouldn't tell me.
他说了什么
Well, what did he tell you?
足以让我认定  如果无人调查
Enough for me to know it would be unethical
是不道德的
if somebody didn't look into this.
但你不能去调查  所以你想让我和哈维去
But you can't, so you want me to get Harvey to.
是你说服他接了我的案子
Well, you convinced him to look into my case
他当时并不想  不是吗
when he didn't want to, didn't you?
这不一样  我们不接这种案子
This is different. We don't take cases like this.
或许吧
Maybe,
但我相信你既然能说服哈维
but I believe a man who can convince Harvey
雇佣一个从未上过法学院的人
to hire someone who never went to law school
也能说服他为此事破例
could convince him to make an exception for this.
什么
What?
他没告诉你我知道了
He didn't tell you I know.
没有
No, he didn't.
我知道了
Well, I do.
但我要你做这件事  跟我知情
But what I'm asking you to do and me knowing
毫无关系
have nothing to do with each other.
多谢
I appreciate that.
那么你会让他接案子吗
Does that mean that you're gonna tell him to take the case?
我有个更好的主意
I have a better idea.
有空吗
Got a second?
当然  什么事
Of course. What do you need?
我要你签字批准我的度假请求
I'd like you to sign off on my vacation request.
巴黎
Paris.
我从未听你提起过巴黎啊
I've never heard you talk about Paris.
是没有  但我听你提起过
No, but I have heard you talk about it,
所以我要带你去
which is why I'm taking you.
你要邀我跟你一起去巴黎吗
Are you asking me to go to Paris with you?
我已经这么做了
I believe I just did.
杰夫  你知道我
Jeff, do you have any idea
现在有多忙吗
how much is on my plate right now?
我知道  哈维已经答应替你应付一切了
Actually, I do, all of which Harvey has agreed to cover.
你还找了哈维
You went to Harvey with this.
我想先来找你的
Well, I would have come to you first,
但那就不算是个惊喜了
but then it really wouldn't be a surprise.
我想想吧
I'll think about it.
慢慢想
Take all the time you need.
但与此同时
But in the meantime,
我会考虑一下我还可以带这里的谁出去玩
I'll be thinking about who else around here I can take.
是嘛
Really?
你好自信啊
Well, you're awfully sure of yourself.
你以为我没注意到诺玛看我的眼神吗
You think I haven't seen the way Norma looks at me?
还喊我黑种马
Calls me the black stallion.
诺玛
Norma.
接个案子
Taking a case.
什么案子
What kind of case?
管他呢
What does it matter?
如果不是出了问题
Because you wouldn't be announcing it like that
你就不会那么说了
if there wasn't something wrong.
这个案子是吉拉德教授给的
It's a case that came from professor Gerard.
什么
What?
一名自由铁路的前雇员
A man who used to work at Liberty Rail
称事故的真实缘故遭到了掩盖
says the real cause of the crash was covered up.
那就叫他去找
Then refer him to a firm
接告密者案子的律所  我们不接
that takes whistle-blower cases, because we don't.
我不会那么做
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
那就别做  但这里没有
Then don't, but there's a reason
接告密者案子的律师是有原因的
lawyers who take whistle-blower cases don't work here,
因为大公司
and it's because corporations
不喜欢敲诈大师
don't appreciate shakedown artists.
如果不是敲诈呢
And what if this isn't a shakedown?
你怎么知道
And how do you know it isn't?
我只知道无辜者死去了
What I know is that innocent people died--
有母亲  父亲  儿子  女儿
Mothers and fathers and sons and daughters--
如果有人掩盖了事实真相
and if somebody's covering up why that happened
而我则能加以制止  我会做的
and I can stop it, then I'm going to.
我说你不能做
And I said you're not.
你还说吉拉德教授
Well, but you also said that professor Gerard
不知道我的秘密呢
didn't know my secret.
哈维  我知道他不会说出去
Harvey, I know, I know he'll never tell anyone,
会有人找到一个会说出去的人
but someday, someone's gonna find out who will,
我就完了
and I'll be done.
迈克  他不...
Mike, he's not--
哈维  我陷入这个烂摊子
Harvey, I got into this whole thing
就是为了帮助他人
so that I could try to help people,
我不知道我还有多少时间
and I don't know how much time I have left,
所以求你
so please,
让我尽力去帮助这些人吧
let me try and help these people.
那你得确保
Then you better make damn sure
这个告密者不是在骗人
this whistle-blower isn't full of shit.
早啊  女士
Bonjour, madame.
你用法语问好正合我意
Oh, I'm so glad you started with that French bullshit,
因为我正想跟你说这个
because that's what I want to talk to you about.
我知道
I know.
没想到会有人求我同意带你去巴黎
Never thought I'd have someone ask my permission to take you to Paris.
你很清楚杰夫那不是求你同意
You know damn well that's not what Jeff did.
杰西卡  你究竟想说什么
Jessica, what exactly do you want to talk about?
我想知道你为什么清空了我的安排
I want to know why you cleared my schedule.
因为杰夫要我做的
Because Jeff asked me to,
而且我都不记得你多久没去度假了
and I can't remember the last time you took a vacation.
那你多久没度假了
When's the last time you took a vacation?
在认真谈恋爱的人又不是我
I'm not the one in a serious relationship.
那你就跑来给我当红娘吗
Oh, so you're playing matchmaker for me now?
我没想当红娘
Oh, I'm not playing anything.
是你自己说  你必须做个选择
And you were the one who said you had to choose
到底要雇他  还是要跟他约会
between hiring him and continuing to see him.
我后来改主意了
And then I changed my mind.
我不想你犯我犯过的错误
And I don't want you to make the same mistake I did.
你指什么
What are you talking about?
我应该多花点时间跟斯科特在一起
I should have taken some time with Scottie.
杰夫和我  跟你和斯科特不一样
Jeff and I are not you and scottie.
杰西卡  你选择去度假
Jessica, take a vacation.
还是不去度假  都随便
Don't take a vacation.
他跑到我这里  求我帮忙
The man came in here, asking me for help
因为他想跟你离开这
because he wants to go away with you,
我答应  是因为我不想阻碍你们
and I said yes because I'm not gonna be the reason he can't.
皮尔逊-斯佩克特  您想接哪里
Pearson Specter, how may I direct your call?
-路易  有空吗  -没有
- Louis, do you have a minute? - No, I don't.
好吧  你在干什么
Okay. What are you doing?
皮尔逊-斯佩克特  您想接哪里
Pearson Specter, how may I direct your call?
-听到吗  -皮尔逊-斯佩克特  您想接哪里
- You hear? - Pearson Specter, how may I direct your call?
喂  皮尔逊-斯佩克特
Hello? Pearson Specter...
听见了吗
You hear that?
利特呢
Where's the Litt?
每通电话都好像在抽我嘴巴
Every call is like a slap in the face.
路易  名字说得简洁
Louis, it's standard practice for a law firm
是一个律所的标准做法
to shorten their name on the phone.
现在公然蔑视我是标准做法了吗
So blatant disrespect is standard practice now?
那不是蔑视你  那是...
It's not disrespect. It's just...
你是说你父亲
You're telling me that your father doesn't
不让他们在接电话时说
have them answer the phone,
"兰德-考德-赞恩"
"Rand, Kaldore, Zane"?
你还真说对了
Actually, no, he doesn't,
我想你也得承认  大家都尊敬我父亲
and I think you'd agree that people respect my father.
除非你又想说
Unless you want to go back to telling me
他是个不怎么样的律师
that he's a shady lawyer.
得了瑞秋  那时我在气头上
Come on, Rachel, that was when I was mad at you.
我就是为了这个来找你的
Which is actually why I wanted to come and talk to you.
我想感谢你原谅了迈克
I want to thank you for forgiving Mike.
这对我意义重大
It--it means a lot to me.
现在你能别再纠结那个电话
Now, can you stop obsessing over the phone
好好听我说吗
long enough to hear that?
很抱歉  瑞秋
I'm sorry, Rachel,
但我做不到
but I can't.
现在我要去炒了那个前台
And now I have to go rip that receptionist a new ass--
路易  如果你成为冠名合伙人后
Louis, if one of your first acts as name partner
第一个举动就是炒前台
is to rip the receptionist to shreds,
那你余生都会为此悔恨的
you'll regret that for the rest of your life.
随他去吧
Just let it go.
随他去
Let it go.
事情会自己回归正轨
Things will run their course.
瑞秋  你说得对
You know what, Rachel? You're right.
而且  很高兴我们又是朋友了
And by the way, I'm glad that we're friends again.
太好了
Good.
皮尔逊-斯佩克特
Pearson Specter...
哈维  今天下午三点半你要做什么
Harvey, what are you doing at 3:30 this afternoon?
怎么了
Why?
我有大新闻  可又不希望你反应过激
I have some news, and I don't want you to overreact.
什么新闻
What is it?
杰夫瑞·本德尔想见你
Jeffrey Bender wants to meet with you.
他听说我们正处理一个告密者的案子
He heard we're taking a whistle-blower case,
他想让我们放弃
and he wants us to drop it.
放松点  我来处理杰夫瑞·本德尔的问题
Relax, I'll take care of Jeffrey Bender.
等等  你不想
Wait a second, you're not gonna try
在迈克开始闹事之前
to cut Mike's legs out from under him
-先砍掉他的腿吗  -砍了有用吗
- before he even gets started? - What's the point?
反正他会一直烦我  直到我说不会放弃
He'd just bother me until I agreed not to anyway.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
你哑口无言了
You have no idea what to say.
今天是几号  我要记下来
What's the date today? I want to write this down.
猜怎么着
You know what?
今天七号  月份名称是"去你的"
It's the seventh of kiss my ass,
明天是八号  月份名称是"自己安排你见鬼的会议吧"
and tomorrow is the eighth of set your own goddamn meetings.
那是玛雅人的历法吗
Is that the Mayan calendar?
不是  那是唐娜历法
Nope, that's the Donna calendar.
我要记录在案  我说得你哑口无言了
I got you. For the record, I got you.
好吧  能否再说一次
All right, take me through it one more time.
很简单
It's simple.
每列车的每节车厢上都装着车轴
There are axles on all the cars in all the trains,
车轴上都有感应器以防车轴过热
And those axles have sensors to make sure they don't overheat.
你是说火车出事
So you're saying that the train crashed
是因为热感应器失灵了
because the heat sensors failed.
我是说所有列车的感应器
I'm saying that all the heat sensors
都失灵了
on the entire fleet were faulty,
而且他们早就知道
and they knew about it.
那你事故前为什么不出面
Then why didn't you come forward with this before?
你问他们因我告密而炒了我之前吗
You mean before they fired me for coming forward with it?
这正好说到我下个问题
Which brings me to my next question.
你过去六年换了四份不同工作
You've had four different jobs in the last six years.
你想说什么
What are you getting at?
我想知道为什么
I want to know why.
我老是搬家
I move around.
这在我们这行不算奇怪
It's not uncommon in my business.
老是搬家  还是工作得不好
Move around or keep failing?
我被炒是因为告密
I got fired for blowing the whistle,
不是因为做不好工作
not for messing up on the job.
你的绩效考核可不是这么说的
That's not what your last performance review says.
绩效考核算个屁
I don't give a shit what it says.
他们用它当借口来炒我鱿鱼
They used that as an excuse to fire me,
我告密之前的绩效
and my reviews before I came forward
可是非常好的
passed with flying colors.
我是个可靠的工人
I'm a solid worker.
你以为我是怎么得到这份工作的
How the hell do you think I got this?
我知道你的绩效很好
I know your reviews are stellar.
我需要的是一些其他的
What I need to know is if there's anything out there
我们尚未掌握的资料
that we don't have,
因为他们会尽其所能地找我们麻烦
because they are gonna come at us any way they can,
而他们一旦动手
and when they do,
出问题的就不是热感应器
it's not gonna be about heat sensors,
而是你了
it's gonna be about you.
我就算做世界上最坏的人也没所谓
Yeah, I don't care if I'm the worst guy in the world.
但我知道  那公司里除我之外
I know I'm not the only guy in that company
还有人知道感应器全都坏了
that knows those sensors are faulty.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
你说有份报告是什么意思
What do you mean, there's a report?
事故之后出的
Done after the crash
说明了部件缺陷才是事故的真正原因
that showed a defective part was the real cause,
而非设计缺陷
not engineer error.
那个告密的人说的吗
Says the whistle-blower.
这上说的
Says these.
这是指令做报告的备忘录
That's a memo ordering the report
另有封电子邮件能确认它的存在
and another email acknowledging its existence.
我们逮到他们了
We got 'em.
-没错  -安排会面
- We do. - Set a meeting.
让他们去说  然后狠狠逼迫他们一下
Let them do the talking, then drop the hammer,
再在他们搞清被谁狠击之前
and stick a settlement down their throat
安排和解
before they know what hit them.
我很感谢你的建议  哈维
I appreciate the advice, Harvey.
但这次我要亲手掌握定音锤
But this time I'm going in with the hammer in my hand,
我要好好决断一下
And I am coming out swinging.
好吧  伶牙俐齿的  你想要多少
Okay, big talker, how much you asking for?
四千万
40 million.
开玩笑的吧
Are you kidding me?
不费劲就能让他们出十倍于这个的价钱
They'll pay ten times that without even trying.
但如果我要他们承认自己的过失
Not when I tell them they're gonna have to admit
可能就不会了
what they did.
-你疯了吗  -不  没疯
- Are you nuts? - No, I am not.
我们不能封存这份和解
We are not sealing this settlement,
你说话之前我再强调一下  这是我的案子
And before you say another word, this is my case.
我不在乎这是谁的案子
I don't care whose case it is.
他们绝不会承认自己的所作所为
They're never going to admit what they did.
选个高价  随他们封存档案吧
Pick a higher number and let them seal it.
哈维  是你让我证明这不是勒索
Harvey, you told me to prove this wasn't a shakedown.
现在又让我收钱帮他们隐瞒
Now you want me to take money to cover things up?
你知道这叫什么吗  这就是勒索
You know what that is? A shakedown!
无理取闹才叫勒索
A shakedown is when your case has no merit.
这才是正确的处理方法
This is the way things work.
况且  这事悄悄和解
Not to mention, if we quietly settle,
我们就不用担心吓跑客户了
we don't have to worry about scaring away our clients.
所以这才是正确的处理方法
That's why it's the way things work.
哈维  车祸死人了
Harvey, people died in this crash!
无论自由铁路承认什么  他们都无法复生
And they're not coming back, no matter what Liberty Rail admits.
你真是个冷血无情的混蛋
You are such a cold, heartless son of a bitch.
这跟你父母的事无关
And this isn't about your parents,
你可以尽情地逼迫他们
so back them into whatever corner you want,
但等他们拒绝承认自己的所作所为
but when they refuse to admit what they did,
你不许闹到上庭那步
you are not going to trial.
少插手我的案子
Stay out of my case.
真香啊
Something smells delicious.
我在为我们做晚饭  但还得等一会
I'm making us dinner, but it won't be ready for a while.
很好  那我们可以趁这时间
Good, that means we have time
过一遍我的推荐路线
to go over my proposed itinerary.
我不记得答应你了
I don't recall saying yes.
我计划我们可以
I thought that we would start
从罗丹[雕塑家]雕塑展私人游开始
with a private tour of the Rodin.
罗丹啊
Oh, the Rodin.
那个雕塑花园我都去过十几遍了
God, I must have visited that sculpture garden a dozen times.
那幸亏我在那里给我们
Then I'm so glad that I arranged for us to have a picnic
安排了一个野餐
while we're there,
我们可以一边吃
and during that picnic,
一边回忆一周前
we can reminisce about the week before,
我们在拉丁区[法国巴黎]彻夜跳舞的情景
where we danced the night away in the Latin Quarter.
是吗
We did?
或者可以谈谈我们如何在卢瓦尔河谷
Mm, or we'll talk about how we'll end the trip
结束我们的旅程
in the loire valley,
我们在塞纳河上啜饮红酒
where we will sip wine along the Seine.
杰夫  真是完美的旅程  你怎么知道的
Jeff, this trip is perfect. How did you know?
我知道你喜欢巴黎  就从那点开始想
I know you've always loved Paris, so I started there.
后来我联系了你妹妹
And then I called your sister.
都是为了我
You did that for me?
是啊
I did.
那你怎么说
So what do you say?
我说...
I say...
如果你知道我在做什么菜
If you knew what I was cooking,
你就知道我的回答了
you'd already know my answer.
看起来像法国菜
Looks French.
所以你明知道你会答应
So you let me go through all that even though
还跟我欲拒还迎
you knew you were gonna say yes the entire time?
我这么做你不高兴吗
Aren't you glad I did?
当然  杰西卡
Yes, Jessica.
我很高兴
Yes, I am.
唐娜  你来干什么
Donna, what are you doing here?
我来是因为我再也受不了了
I'm here because I can't take it anymore.
什么
What?
这地方一点生机都没有  我再也受不了了
This place has no life, and I can't take it anymore.
你就打算用仙人掌增加生机
And that's gonna add life?
如果我给弄点难照顾的
If I gave you something too needy,
会吓到你  而你会任它死去
it would intimidate you, and you would let it die.
你指望我相信你真是为这事来的吗
You expect me to believe that's why you're really here?
当然没有
Of course not.
我是来阻止你
I'm here to stop you from doing
接下来一小时要做的事
what you're gonna do in an hour:
搞砸迈克的会面
crash Mike's meeting.
唐娜  我不能任由他拿我们的律所冒险
Donna, I can't have him risking our other business.
那只是个委托人  帮忙瞒一下就好
It was one client, and you covered it.
如果他搞上法庭
And if he drags this to trial,
就会涉及到所有委托人了
It will be every client.
-这可不一定  -肯定会
- You don't know that. - Yes, I do.
那就相信他能自己接受这一点
Then trust him to accept that on his own.
-唐娜  -哈维
- Donna-- - Harvey,
你什么时候才能让他自己做主
when are you gonna let him be his own man?
自己做主  他已经失控了
His own man? He's out of control.
他把那些受害人当成了自己的父母
He's identifying these people with his parents.
而你失控是因为你无法
And you're out of control because you can't
让自己跟他分离开
separate yourself from him.
你别管这件事
Okay, you need to stay out of it.
我不管  但你说过吉利斯工业的案子
And I will, but you said you made a mistake
你没信任他是个错误
not trusting Mike with Gillis Industries.
我是在提醒你别再犯同样的错误
I'm telling you, don't make that mistake again.
这里是皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所  您找哪位
Pearson Specter, how may I direct your call?
兰德-考德-赞恩律所
Rand, Kaldore, Zane.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
你好  骗子
Hello, liar.
-你说什么  -兰德-考德-赞恩
- Excuse me? - Rand, Kaldore, Zane.
知道这是什么吗
You know what that is?
这是兰德-考德-赞恩律所的前台应答语
That's how they answer the phone at Rand, Kaldore, Zane.
-路易  对不起  -收起你的假惺惺
- Louis, I'm sorry. - Oh, save your sorrys.
你认识前台那个接待员吗
Do you know the receptionist at the front desk?
认识  她叫爱丽丝
Yes, her name is Elise.
很好  等你辞了她你可以用这个名字
Good, you can use her name when you fire her.
我无权解雇别人
I don't have the authority to fire people,
但我刚跟她谈过
But I did just talk to her.
是吗
You did?
让她改正了  那就好
To set her straight. That's good.
不  不好
No, not good.
她主动来找我
She came to see me.
她说你一直在骚扰她
She said that you've been harassing her.
什么
What happened?
她说你打给她然后挂断了50多次
She said that you called and hung up on her over 50 times.
什么  她怎么知道是我
What? How did she even know it was me?
因为是你的办公室座机号
Because you called from your office.
那也不叫骚扰  因为无关性事
Well, it wasn't harassment because it wasn't sexual.
她还说你出电梯的时候
Well, she also said that you were leering at her
总向她抛媚眼
when you stepped off the elevator.
我才没有
I wasn't leering!
我是为她接电话时说的话感到生气
I was mad about how she answered the phone.
路易  你为什么那么做不重要
Louis, it doesn't matter why you did it.
她觉得被侵犯了
She felt violated.
不如你去告诉她实情
Well, you know what, you tell her it's not like that,
然后把她踹出门去
and then you violate her ass out the door.
路易  你就想当个这样的冠名合伙人吗
Louis, is this really the kind of name partner you want to be?
不  我想当一个前台接电话时
No, I want to be the kind of name partner
大声念出名字的冠名合伙人
that has his name said on the goddamn phone.
那么为了解雇她
Okay, well, in order to fire her
并避免遭到骚扰起诉
without getting sued for harassment,
你就得解雇所有客服人员
you'd have to fire the entire support staff,
你我都清楚  这是不可能发生的
and you and I both know that that's never going to happen.
我们不能解雇所有客服人员
We are not firing all of our support staff.
你的名字排第一个  你当然站着说话不腰疼
Well, it's easy for you to say, being that your name is first.
你在说什么...
What are you talking--
杰西卡  我说的是尊重
Jessica, I am talking about respect.
尊  重  你好好想想它对我的意义
R-e-s-p-e-c-t, find out what it means to me.
但我猜我还是自己想办法
But I guess I'll just find my own way
得到自己应得的尊重吧
to be treated how I deserve.
我知道我会后悔这么问
I know I'm gonna regret asking this.
路易  你究竟在说什么
Louis, tell me specifically what it is you're talking about.
前台接电话说的是"皮尔逊-斯佩克特"
They are answering the phones, "Pearson Specter,"
而不是"皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特律所"
Not "Pearson Specter Litt."
路易
Louis--
你不相信  你自己听
You don't believe me? Check it yourself.
我不会去骚扰客服人员
I'm not harassing our support staff.
这不是骚扰
It's not harassment, god damn it!
路易
Louis!
杰西卡  我感觉他们故意
Jessica, it's like they've been specifically instructed
落下我的名字的
to leave my name off.
你想太多了
Now you're just being paranoid.
不是我想太多  他们只是没适应过来
I am not paranoid. They're in lockstep.
肯定有人买通他们这么干的
I'm telling you, someone paid them off.
路易  这太疯狂了
Louis, that's insane,
但是如果你想要他们报你的名字
But if you want them to say your name,
我会让他们报你名字的
I will get them to say your name.
杰西卡  有什么需要帮忙吗
Jessica, what can I do for you?
你可以向我解释一下为什么你付钱
You can explain to me why you paid our reception staff
让前台接电话的时候别说路易的名字
not to say louis' name when they answer the phone.
-谁说是我干的  -他们说的
- Who says I did that? - They do.
妈的
God damn it.
我给他们好大一笔  让他们瞒路易
I paid them good money to keep louis
至少一个月
from finding out for at least a month.
他的确没发现
He hasn't found out.
不是他让他们开的口  是我
It wasn't him who got them to crack, it was me.
就算是这样  我也要求退款
Even still, I'm asking for a refund.
杰夫  我很认真
Jeff, I'm serious about this.
我知道你对路易名字上墙的方式很不齿
I know you're pissed about how he got his name on the door,
但我需要你停战和解
But I need you to bury the hatchet.
-我没打算停战  -为什么不呢
- Well, I'm not gonna do that. - Why not?
因为每次看到他那张贼眉鼠眼的脸
Because every single time I see his rat face,
我就会想到他敲诈了你
I think about him blackmailing you,
这让我想上去
And it makes me want to walk over to him
把他俩胳膊都卸了
and rip his arms off his body,
那个小小的电话恶作剧只是
and that little phone prank was just my way
我防止自己暴力行为的方法
of keeping myself from doing something like that.
我懂你
I understand,
也很感谢你这样做
and I do appreciate it,
但是我并不是要求你为他而和解
But I'm not asking you to do it for him.
是为了我
I'm asking you to do it for me.
罗斯先生
Mr. Ross.
我对你文件的想法就是
All I can say about your filing is that I think
你很有写科幻小说的前途
you might have a career writing fiction.
可你要是不提交那份我们需要的报告
And if you don't hand over that report we're requesting,
你就会有蹲大狱的前途了
You're gonna have a career behind bars.
你来不是为了那份报告
You're not here for that report.
而是为了我委托人数目可观的支票
You're here to strong arm my client into a big, fat check.
很抱歉是由我来告诉你
I'm sorry to be the one to tell you this,
但巨额支票也不能帮你们摆脱此事
but a big, fat check isn't gonna get you out of this.
-是这样吗  -废话当然了
- Is that a fact? - Sure as hell is,
因为我们都知道  那份报告
Because we both know that report
声明你们对这起事故负责
says you're responsible for this accident,
但是除非你们承认  否则和解免谈
and we're not settling anything without you admitting it.
但是我们不会承认根本没做的事情
And we're not admitting something we didn't do.
这是什么
What the hell is this?
你说你想要报告
Well, you wanted the report.
给你了
Here it is.
你的委托人说它存在不是假话
Your client wasn't lying about its existence.
但其他内容就都是骗人了
He was just lying about everything else.
我们对热感应器进行了反复测试
We ran repeated tests on our heat sensors,
每一次它们都通过了
And they passed every one.
你胡说
This is bullshit.
在胡说的是
The only thing that's bullshit
乔·亨德森
is Joe Henderson.
他根本就不在乎事故
He doesn't care about the accident.
他只是想敲诈我们
All he's trying to do is shake us down,
一如他之前四份工作中的行为
Exactly like he did at his last four jobs.
那又是什么
What the hell is that?
他之前的四桩官司
His last four lawsuits.
你觉得就因为记录都封存了
Did you think we wouldn't find out about them
我们就找不出了吗
just because the records were sealed?
罗斯先生  你的委托人
Mr. Ross, your client's been playing
一直都在玩告密的把戏
The whistle-blower lottery for years.
他从来没赢过
He's never won before.
这次也不会赢
He's not going to win today.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch,
你每做一份工作
you tried to blow the whistle
都会告发泄密  现在他们知道了
at every job you've ever had, and now they know it!
小声点
Keep your voice down.
你  不  等你不拿瞎话应付我了
You-- no, I'll keep my voice down
我再小声点
when you stop bullshitting me.
那些声明本应该是被封存的
Those claims were supposed to be sealed.
我不在乎它们本来应该怎样
I don't care what they were supposed to be.
他们找到了  你本该在这之前告诉我
They found them, and you were supposed to tell me about them.
如果我说了  你会怎么做呢
And what would you have done if I did?
我会跟他们说一样的话
I would've said what they said,
你根本不在乎他们做了什么
that you don't give a shit about what they did!
你只是想借此生财罢了
You're just looking to get rich.
你觉得我会拿我的工作和一切
You think I would've risked my job
去冒险求那虚无缥缈的东西吗
and everything that I have for nothing?
你说什么
Excuse me?
我说了  我没看出你那一千块西服里
I said, I don't see you working out of the goodness
包着出于善意而工作的心
of your heart in your $1,000 suit.
你根本不了解我  也不知道我做事的动机
You have no idea who I am or why I do things.
现在我告诉你  你不需要担心我的过去
And I told you, you don't have to be concerned about my history
因为我告诉你的都是实话
because what I'm telling you is true.
照这个来看可不是
Not according to this.
你说这份报告能让我们抓住他们的把柄
That's the report that you said gave us all the leverage
但是他们却说它证明了他们的清白
and they say proves them innocent.
那份报告在胡扯
That report is bullshit,
因为我跟你说  那些感应器不管用
because I'm telling you, those sensors didn't work,
而那就是事故的起因
and that was the cause of that accident.
要是你之前信誉好点
Well, I might have a leg to stand on
我还有点理由支持你
if you had any credibility at all.
现在我自己都不信你
How the hell am I supposed to get a jury to believe you
我又怎么让陪审团信你
when I'm not even sure I do?
你来这干嘛
What are you doing here?
我来告诉你该给前台打电话了
I'm here to tell you to call the front desk.
让我猜猜
Oh, let me guess.
杰西卡告诉你他们不肯把我的名字一起报出来
Jessica told you they won't say my name
你觉得这很好笑
and you thought it was hilarious.
你说对了  很好笑
You're right, I did.
你为什么不滚出我的办公室
Why don't you get the hell out of my office
滚到其它地方笑去呢
and go laugh somewhere else?
你这是想打我了
Oh, you want to hit me now?
呵呵  去问问迈克·罗斯我的锁喉术怎么样
Yeah, well, why don't you go ask Mike Ross about my headlock?
因为哥像老虎钳一样
'cause it's a goddamn vice.
皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特律师事务所
Pearson Specter Litt,
请问转接哪位律师
How may I direct your call?
是你干的
It was you.
对  是我干的
Yes, it was me,
但我已经把它改正了  所以...
But I fixed it, so...
你可以不用再担心律所的人是否尊敬你了
You can stop worrying if everybody at the firm respects you,
因为他们的确尊敬你
because they do.
除了你
Everyone except you.
不  路易  包括我
No, Louis, including me.
我可能看不惯你名字上墙的方式
Listen, I may not like how you got your name on the wall,
但那不代表你的名字不应该在上面
But that doesn't mean it shouldn't be up there.
恭喜  路易
Congratulations, Louis.
谢谢  杰夫
Thanks, Jeff.
我们这周是不是还能约个酒呢
Hey, maybe we can even get drinks this week.
-谁冠名谁买单  -成交
- Name partner buys. - Deal.
说好了
Done.
咖啡可以留下  但我不会起来的
You can leave the coffee, but I'm not getting up.
迈克  你已经连续工作7个小时了
Mike, you've been working for seven hours straight.
-你需要休息  -我之所以工作7个小时
- You need a break. - I've been working for seven hours
是因为如果我在想出解决办法之前
because if I tell Harvey
告诉哈维发生的事情
What's going on before I have a fix,
他就要终止这件事了
He is gonna pull the plug.
那可能这件事是该结束了
Well, then maybe the plug needs to be pulled.
瑞秋  就因为乔·亨德森
Rachel, just because Joe Henderson is
是个满嘴胡话的原告并不代表着
a bullshit plaintiff doesn't mean
他们没有掩饰什么事情
they didn't cover things up.
也不代表他们真的隐瞒了什么
It doesn't mean that they did.
那好吧
Okay, fine.
如果他明知道那份报告对案子无益
Why would he ask for that report
为什么还会要呢
if he knew it would hurt our case?
-我不懂  -我也不懂
- I don't know. - I don't know either,
所以我才需要更多的时间
which is why I need more time.
那你就得去说服哈维让你继续跟下去
Well, then you need to convince harvey to let you keep going,
要是你不说而他又发现了的话...
because if you don't and he finds out--
不会被他发现的
He is not gonna find out.
迈克  我是不会告诉他的
Mike, he's not gonna find out from me,
但就这六个月来我在这里的经验
But if I've learned one thing in the last six months
如果他从别人那知道了这事
of working here, it's that if he finds out from somebody else,
你会后悔的
you're gonna regret it.
是来告诉我你决定要度假了吗
You come here to tell me you're taking that vacation?
我是来问问迈克·罗斯什么时候
I came by to ask when Mike Ross started taking
接了那桩告密者的案子
whistle-blower cases.
杰西卡
Jessica--
我希望你能在此事失控前
I want you to put the brakes on him
就阻止他干傻事
before this gets out of control.
我不会那么做
Well, I'm not gonna do that.
-哈维  -杰西卡  只是个案子而已
- Harvey. - Jessica, it's one case.
他要我信任他  我也打算这么做
He asked me to trust him, and I'm gonna do it,
而且如果你要想好好度个假
and if you're ever gonna be able to enjoy a vacation,
就要信任我
you're gonna have to trust me.
好吧  晚安
All right. Good night.
一路顺风
Bon voyage.
你知道这句话的意思不是晚安对吧
You do know that doesn't mean "Good night."
当然了
Of course I do.
那你知道法语怎么说晚安吗
Do you know how to say "Good night" in French?
怎么  你觉得我是个原始人吗
What, do you think I'm some kind of neanderthal?
你一句法语都不会说  对吧
You don't know one word of French, do you?
三口之家
Mennage en trois.
你这个蠢货
You're an idiot.
四口之家
Mennage en quatre.
五口之家
Mennage en cinq.
我能进来吗
Can I come in?
怎么回事啊
What's going on?
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
说吧
I'm listening.
自由铁路公司报告直接否定了我们的立论
Liberty Rail's report directly contradicts our claim.
那确实是个大麻烦
That's a big damn problem.
我相信我的委托人  哈维
I believe my client, Harvey.
根据什么相信  直觉吗
Based on what, your gut?
不  我找到了写报告的人
No, I found the guy who wrote the report.
他去澳大利亚了  假期时长不定
He's on indefinite leave in Australia,
所以我们无法传唤他
where we can't subpoena him.
那双方一样口说无凭啊
So it's our word against theirs.
所以我才来找你
Which is why I'm here.
乔·亨德森过去六年中索赔了四次
Joe Henderson made four other claims in the last six years.
-你玩儿我呢吧  -哈维
- You're shitting me. - Harvey--
够了  我要结束这个案子
That's it. I'm pulling the plug.
我就知道
I knew it.
我就知道只要稍微遇到一点挫折
I knew you would bail on me the second this thing
你就会丢下我不管
hit the smallest bump.
丢下你不管
Bail on you?
我支持你是因为你告诉我你会赢
I backed you because you told me you had a case.
我可以赢  我说了是他们买通了出报告的人
I do have a case. I told you they got to this guy.
但你没法证明
And you got no proof of that.
如果这是你的案子
And if this were your case,
你肯定会求我帮你打下去
you would be begging me for help to get it.
但现在这不是我的  是你的
It's not my case. It's yours.
现在你要让陪审团相信
And now you're asking a jury
是这些人伪造了报告
to believe these guys fabricated a report
就凭一个职业告密者的话
based on the word of a career whistle-blower.
不  我是在要求你相信
No, I'm asking you to believe it.
我信什么不重要
It doesn't matter what I believe.
这人就是个勒索犯
This guy is a goddamn shakedown artist,
我要叫停
and I'm pulling the plug.
我不在乎他是什么
I don't care what he is.
但我不是个勒索犯
I'm not a goddamn shakedown artist!
-迈克  -哈维  你跟我说过
- Mike -- - Harvey, you told me that
这些人不是我的父母
those people weren't my parents,
但他们总是某些人的父母
but they are somebody's parents.
拜托了
Please.
再给你24小时
You got 24 hours.
你知道乱丢垃圾是违法的对吧
You know it's against the law to litter, don't you?
有事吗  唐娜
What do you want, Donna?
我知道你去见哈维了
I know you went to see Harvey.
你知道他就是希望我失败
You know that he wants me to fail.
不是这样的
That's not true.
现在我毫无头绪  而他就只给了我一天
I don't have anything, and he only gave me a day.
但如果他希望你失败
And if he wanted you to fail,
就一秒也不会给你
he wouldn't have given you another second.
你知道他觉得我这么做是因为我父母对吧
You know he thinks this is about my parents, right?
那是吗
Is it?
也许吧
Maybe it is,
但这些人的所作所为更可恨
but what these people did is a million times worse
因为他们知道会发生这样的情况
because they knew it could happen.
等等  他们知道会发生这样的事
Wait a second -- they knew this could happen,
却没有修理吗
and they didn't fix it before?
没错  唐娜  而且他们决定赌运气
Yeah, Donna, and then they -- they rolled the dice.
那现在怎么办
Well, what about now?
那些火车还是残次品吗
Are those trains still messed up?
因为如果这样  那他们禽兽不如
Because that would make them monsters.
他们是禽兽不如  但不修理就是犯傻
They are monsters, but that would also make them idiots,
但他们不傻
and they're not idiots.
你什么意思
Well, what are you talking about?
他们现在肯定已经修好传感器了
Well, they must have fixed the sensors by now;
否则如果再出事  他们就得进监狱
Otherwise if it happened again, they'd all go to jail.
那如果他们修好了传感器
Well, if they fixed the sensors,
肯定有份纸质的报告存在
then there has to be - a paper trail.
当然有了
Of course there is.
那你只要找到就好了
Then all you have to do is get it.
你以为我一晚上都在干什么
What do you think I've been trying to figure out all night?
找文件干什么呀  传讯报告人就好了呀
What's to figure out? Subpoena it.
只有一个小问题  哈维只给了我一天
Yeah, there's only one problem. Harvey only gave me 24 hours.
但现在你有了头绪
But now that you've come up with this,
也许哈维会改主意呢
maybe Harvey will change his mind.
唐娜  我的理论是我无法证明
Donna, I have a theory that I can't prove and an opposition
而且我的敌人还可以篡改证据
that's shown they're willing to alter evidence.
他不会改主意的  这你也清楚
He's not gonna change his mind, and you know it.
总有其他办法的
There's got to be another way.
唐娜  我很感激你想帮忙的心
Donna, look, I appreciate what you're doing,
但除非你有办法解决此事
but unless you have this other way in your pocket,
否则就别打扰我了
please, just leave me alone
让我自己想办法解决吧
and let me try and think this thing through.
不  我才不管他怎么说
No! I don't care what he says.
这可是个在查案件
It's an active goddamn investigation,
-而且我也不打算  -这儿不能打电话
- and I'm not gonna stand around -- - You can't talk on that here.
稍等一下  查理
Hang on a second, Charlie.
抱歉  我们这个招呼打得不太愉快
I'm sorry, we got off on the wrong foot.
你是叫丹妮尔吗
Is your name Danielle?
牌子上不是都写着吗
That's what it says on the plate, isn't it?
丹妮尔  我是来取文件的
Well, Danielle, I'm here to pick up the documents
我一小时前要过了  如果15秒内
I ordered an hour ago, and if you don't give them to me
你还不给我
in the next 15 seconds,
今天就是你工作的最后一天
today's gonna be your last day.
你没跟我要过
You didn't talk to me.
我说稍等  真是的
I said hold on, damn it.
听着  我没时间跟你玩躲猫猫
Look, I don't have time to play "Who spoke To who."
我从华盛顿跑到这儿来
I am up from DC because, as it is,
是因为我要的文件没有按时送到
these documents weren't sent when they were promised.
-抱歉  你要什么来着  -天哪
- I'm sorry. What is it you need again? - Oh, Jesus Christ.
过去六个月以来的所有维修订单
All the maintenance work orders from the past six months.
没有授权我不能给你
I can't let you have that without authorization.
那好啊  不如现在就给你上司打电话
Well, then by all means, let's call your supervisor,
我们可以顺便告诉他你在这儿玩开心农场
and we can tell him how you'd rather play Farmville
耽误着我的事
than cooperate with me.
你说你是哪来的
Who did you say you're with again?
你听说过国家运输管理局吗
Have you heard of the National Transportation Safety Board?
里面的人会给你想要的文件
They'll give you what you need in the back.
你做了什么
What did you do?
什么也没做啊  你呢
I didn't do anything. What did you do?
别跟我闹  这是此案胜败的关键
Don't give me that. This makes my entire case,
但如果不知道是从哪来的我就没法用
but I can't use it if I don't know where it came from.
看起来好像是来自自由铁路公司的哦
Oh, that looks like it came from Liberty Rail.
那它就突然自己
Oh, oh, yeah, it just happened to walk itself
穿过他们的安保设施跑出来了
over from their secure facility.
也许是有人去了一趟
Well, it's possible that somebody went over there
把它从安保设施里放出来了
and released it from their secure facility.
唐娜  如果我拿着这个去找哈维
Donna, if I go to Harvey with this
告诉他我知道的事  他...
and tell him what I know happened, he--
你不知道  你只是猜测
You don't know. You think.
别跟我玩律师抠词那套  他不会让我用的
Don't lawyer me. He'll never let me use it.
那就别告诉他你猜测的事
Well, then don't tell him what you think happened,
因为如果你说了  他会让你放弃案子
because if you do, he'll make you drop the case.
好吧  眼下  我不关心案子
Okay, right now, I don't care about the case.
我关心你
I care about you.
迈克  我没偷东西
Mike, I didn't steal anything.
我说服对方让我进去了  事情就是这样
I talked my way in, and that's what happened.
你跟他们说这是要发掘一个
Did you tell them this was discovery
针对他们的案子吗
for a case against them?
-没有  -那这材料在庭上是不能采纳的
- No. - Then it's not admissible in court.
那你得想个办法
Well, then you have to figure out a way
不要在庭上用它
to use it not in court,
但别让我帮你想
but don't ask me for my help on that.
我做的已经够多了
I have done enough.
听说你想见我
Heard you wanted to see me.
我听说你跟路易·利特和好了
I take it you patched things up with Louis Litt.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
他想知道你是喜欢运动酒吧
Oh, he wanted to know if you were a sports bar guy
还是葡萄酒吧
or a wine bar guy.
你告诉他我其实更喜欢脱衣舞吧吗
Did you tell him I'm more of a strip club kind of guy?
你真的想跟路易·利特去脱衣舞吧吗
You really want to go to a strip club with Louis Litt?
我其实不想跟任何人去脱衣舞吧
I don't really want to go to a strip club with anyone,
但我10分钟后确实要见个人
but I do have a meeting in 10 minutes,
但见面地点离这里有15分
and it's 15 minutes away.
我只是想告诉你
Oh, I just wanted to tell you
我很感激你跟他和好了
that I appreciate you patching things up with him.
不用谢我
There's no need to thank me.
为我爱的人做什么都愿意
I would do anything for the woman that I love...
跟路易·利特喝酒都行
even get a drink with Louis Litt.
你是来说安德顿软件的事吗
You here to talk about Anderton Software?
你自由铁路的24小时时限已经到了
Because your 24-hour Liberty Rail pass is up.
那我猜我刚收到这封邮件
Then I guess it's a good thing
是个好消息
that just came in the mail for me.
这是什么
What is it?
维修记录
Maintenance records showing
证明他们在出轨时间后6周内
they replaced the heat sensors on all of their trains
更换了所有列车的热传感器
within six weeks after the derailment.
如果他们安全检查没出错  为什么要换呢
Now, why would they do that if they never failed a safety test?
没出错就不会换
They wouldn't.
所以乔·亨德森说的是对的
Which means Joe Henderson was telling the truth.
我能想到他们会用3种方式
I can think of three different ways
解释这行为
they'll explain this away.
除非我们可以在他们发觉前把它记录在案
Not if we can get them on record before they know we have it.
为什么他们不知道我们拿到了这个
And why don't they know we have it?
跟我不知道他们拿到了
The same way I didn't know they got
乔·亨德森的密封记录一个原因
Joe Henderson's sealed records.
这说明你用了点不光明的小手段
Which means you did something sketchy.
哈维  你想花一晚上时间
Harvey, do you want to spend all night asking me
拷问我知道什么不知道什么
exactly what I did or did not do,
还是帮我纠正一件错误的事
or do you want to help me right a wrong?
唐娜
Donna?
跟自由铁路预约取证会
Set a deposition with Liberty Rail,
告诉他们这次不光迈克出席
and tell them this time it won't just be Mike.
马上去
I'm on it.
那是谁
Who the hell is that?
自由铁路的首席执行官
That's the CEO of Liberty Rail.
我知道他是谁  但她呢
Yeah, I know who he is. Who is she?
是他们的律师
That's their lawyer.
你怎么不告诉我她这么辣
Why didn't you tell me she was hot?
因为那跟案件没关系
Because it's not relevant.
-对我来说有关系  -为什么
- It is to me. - Why?
因为她很辣
Because she's hot.
你肯定就是著名的哈维·斯佩克特了
You must be the infamous Harvey Specter.
-你一定是...  - 伊凡·施密斯
- You must be-- - Evan Smith.
我得承认  看到你叫伊凡时
Have to admit, when I saw your name was Evan,
我以为你是男性
I thought you were a man.
我也得承认  看到你叫哈维时
And I have to admit, when I saw your name was Harvey,
我以为你是男性
I thought you were a man.
-我觉得我恋爱了  -我也觉得你是
- I think I'm in love. - I think you are too.
我们赶紧结束  开始正事吗
Okay, can we get this over with?
当然可以
We sure can.
我都不知道你们还能有什么问题
I don't even know how you have any questions at all,
上次会议已经那样了
given our last meeting.
只有几个问题
We just have a few.
麦金泰尔先生  在出轨事件前
Mr. McIntyre, before the derailment,
自由铁路进行了列车热传感器的检测工作
Liberty Rail conducted tests on the heat sensors on its trains.
是吗
Is that correct?
-当然  -为什么要做检测呢
- Of course we did. - And why was that?
我们整个系统都做了检测
We run tests on all our systems.
是常规检测
It's routine.
报告结果是
And the finding of that report
热传感器没有任何问题
is that there were no problems with the heat sensors.
你们是要抓着
Are you going to just ask questions
已经有答案的问题问下去吗
that you already know the answers to?
这是常规问题
It's routine.
传感器没有问题
There weren't any problems with the sensors.
-那你们是常规性地换了传感器吗  -对
- And do you routinely replace the heat sensors? - Yes.
我们每五年更换一次
We replace them every five years
那是我们定期维修的一部分
as part of our regularly scheduled maintenance.
那上次定期维修是什么时候呢
And when was the last regularly scheduled maintenance?
大约两年前
That would be two years ago.
你们不会修理没坏的东西  对吗
And you wouldn't fix something that wasn't broken, right?
当然
Of course not.
我做生意不是为赔钱  先生们
I'm not in the business of wasting money, gentlemen.
我有点疑惑
I'm a bit confused.
如果你做生意不是为赔钱
If you're not in the business of wasting money
传感器又没问题
and there was nothing wrong with those sensors,
那你们最近为什么要把它们全换了
then why did you just replace all of them?
他们没有全换
They didn't replace all of them.
我们希望你的客户来回答问题
I think we'd like your client to answer that question.
你有点为难啊  理查德
You're in a bit of a pickle, Richard.
你不知道说有还是没有好
You don't know whether to say you did or you didn't.
当然  你可以拿自己的命运摇骰子
Of course, you could roll the dice with your own life
就像你对待别人的生活那样
just like you did with other people's.
事实是  没关系
The truth is, it doesn't matter,
因为你已经在摄像机前说
because you already said on camera
你没有更换传感器
you didn't replace those sensors.
可我们有这个
And we have these.
你们从哪弄到这些的
Where'd you get these?
我告诉你我跟乔·亨德森说过的话
I'll tell you what I told Joe Henderson.
从哪弄到的不重要
It doesn't matter where they came from.
重要的是它们在这里
It just matters that they're here.
我得跟我的客户单独聊聊
I need to talk to my client.
好主意
That's a good idea.
你们得好好商量一下
You should discuss how many zeros
赔偿支票上得写几个零
you're gonna write on that check.
还有件事
And one more thing.
你们不只得写一张支票
You're not only gonna write a check.
还得写一份公开道歉信
You're gonna write a public admission
因为车祸里有人丧生了
because people died in that crash.
事情不是这么办的
That's not how this works.
今天它就要这么办
It's how it works today.
你真的要逼他们写公开道歉信吗
You're really gonna force them to make a public admission?
是的  当然
Damn right, I am.
-你是谁  圣雄甘地吗  -总得有人去逼
- Who are you, Mahatma Gandhi? - Somebody has to be.
你太着急赚钱了
You were too busy demanding a bunch of zeros.
我只是在帮你留心
Well, I was just looking out for you.
西装可不会自己付钱
Those suits don't pay for themselves.
对  是不会
No, they don't.
迈克  干得漂亮  你真的变强了
Mike, great job. You really stepped it up.
谢谢  哈维
Thanks, Harvey.
我觉得你也开始进入你的全盛时代了
I think you might be starting to come into your own too.
真的吗
Really?
每场比赛吗
Every single game?
不  只有季后赛
No, just the playoffs.
-两口吗  -两口
- Two sips? - Two sips.
-不多不少  -任何啤酒吗
- No more, no less. - Any beer?
不  不是任何啤酒
Oh, no, not any beer.
米勒淡啤
Miller Lite.
米勒淡啤  不是吧
Miller Lite? What?
但她是女王
But she's a queen.
能跟你说什么呢  她从她爸爸那里学来的
What can I tell you? She got it from her dad.
如果巨人队进入季后赛
Look, if the Giants are in the playoffs
杰西卡没有在他们每个初次进攻后
and Jessica doesn't take two sips of Miller Lite
喝两口米勒淡啤的话
after every single first down,
她就是觉得他们要输了
she thinks they're gonna lose,
完全没办法改变她的想法
and there's no talking her out of it.
经常发生吗  第一次进攻
And those happen a lot, right? First downs?
当然了
They sure do.
她喝醉的时候什么样子
So what is she like when she's drunk?
那下次再聊吧
Well, that's a conversation for another time.
我非常懂你了  老兄
I so feel you, bro.
我要说  路易
You know, I got to say, Louis,
我都快因为捉弄你而内疚了
I almost feel bad about pulling that prank on you.
别内疚
Don't feel bad.
那个恶作剧挺好的
It was a pretty good prank.
好吧
Okay.
再来一杯
One more?
除非你再跟说说杰西卡在家是什么样的
Only if you tell me more about what Jessica's like at home.
不  算了  我要你告诉我
No, screw that, I want you to tell me
皮尔逊·哈德曼时期  她是什么样的
what she was like back when it was Pearson Hardman.
成交
Done.
你要下班了吗
You're heading out for the night?
-再过几分钟  -想喝两杯吗
- In a few minutes. - Want to grab a drink?
庆祝一下吗
Celebrate?
-不行  -为什么不行
- I can't. - Why not?
跟你没关系
Not that it's any of your concern,
但我要跟伊凡·施密斯去喝酒
but I'm having drinks with Evan Smith.
什么  你拿到她的号码了吗
What? You got her number?
没有  她打电话给我了
No, she called me.
她问你要号码了
Oh, she asked for your number?
没有  也没必要  你给她的
No, she didn't have to. You gave it to her.
就在传票上
It was on that subpoena.
我知道你的传票上会写什么
I know what's gonna be on your subpoena.
-那是什么意思  -你知道那是什么意思
- What does that even mean? - You know what it means.
当然了
Sure as hell do.
-你想见我  -没错
- You wanted to see me? - I did.
我猜是因为你听说了自由铁路公司的事情了
I take it you heard about Liberty Rail.
-没错  -瞧瞧
- I did. - See?
没有伤害  没有犯规  也没有客户流失
No harm, no foul, no mass exodus of clients.
我很满意
I'm glad.
你在想什么  杰西卡  你看起来不...
What's on your mind, Jessica? You don't seem--
我知道你跟斯科特说过迈克·罗斯的事
I know you told Scottie about Mike Ross.
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
我也是刚刚才知道
I didn't till just now.
-杰西卡  -我不生气
- Jessica-- - I'm not mad.
我只想知道你为什么想告诉她
I just want to know what made you want to tell her.
那有什么区别
What difference does that make?
因为我也想告诉杰夫有关迈克·罗斯的事情
Because I want to tell Jeff the truth about Mike Ross too.
从你告诉他
What changed between now
有关路易假话到现在发生了什么改变吗
and when you fed him that Louis bullshit?
没什么改变
Nothing's changed.
我只是不想再对他说谎了
I just don't want to lie to him anymore.
他告诉你他爱你  是不是
He told you he loved you, didn't he?
你什么时候开始懂这些事情了
When the hell did you start figuring shit like that out?
我也是刚刚才懂的
I didn't till just now.
那就回答我的问题
Then answer my question.
是什么让你决定告诉斯科特的
What made you decide to tell Scottie?
你真正想知道的不是这些
That's not what you really want to know.
你想知道的是我是否后悔没有早点告诉她
What you want to know is if I wish I told her sooner.
你有吗
Do you?
对  我有
Yes, I do.
瑞秋  需要帮忙吗
Hey, Rachel, what can I do for you?
我只是想过来说声谢谢
I just wanted to come by and say thank you.
-谢什么  -拜托  唐娜
- For what? - Oh, come on, Donna.
迈克告诉我今天你救了他
Mike told me you saved the day.
好吧  你知道
Oh, well, you know,
我从那座着火的楼里救出那些孩子后
after I saved those kids from that burning building,
就有点多余的时间  所以
I had a little extra time, so--
那么今晚你也许该休息会儿了
Well, then maybe you should take the rest of the night off.
为什么
And why is that?
因为超级英雄都这样
Because that's what superheroes do.
18年麦卡伦
Macallan 18.
你很有品位
You got great taste.
我打电话给你很吃惊吗
Surprised I called?
还是那句  你很有品味  但我要说清楚
Like I said, you got great taste, but let me be clear.
如果你要谈和解
You want to talk settlement,
迈克·罗斯不在  我是不会谈的
I can't do it without Mike Ross.
我决不是来谈和解的
I'm definitely not here to talk settlement.
很好  因为有些事没有他我也能做
Good, because there are things I can do without him,
而且做得特别好
exceptionally.
我想给你看段小视频
I want to show you a little video.
什么  你挖到了我高中时
What, did you dig up footage
打锦标赛的视频了吗
from my high school championship?
因为那样我简直唾手可得了
Because that'll make this too easy.
恐怕不是
Afraid not.
那是你的秘书非法获取证据
That's your secretary unlawfully gathering evidence,
意味着我们根本不会达成和解
which means there will be no settlement of any kind.
明天  我就把这段视频发给地检
And tomorrow, I'm sending this to the district attorney.
好好喝吧  帅哥
Enjoy your drink, handsome.
杰西卡
Jessica.
杰夫  有件事我要告诉你
Jeff, there's something I need to tell you.
我也有件事要告诉你
There's something I need to tell you too.
怎么了
What's going on?
我刚刚跟路易喝了些酒
What's going on is I just had drinks with Louis,
为了帮你
you know, as a favor to you.
结果证明他不胜酒力
Turns out he's not so great at holding his liquor.
-他干了什么  -不  他什么也没干
- What did he do? - No, he didn't do anything.
-是你干的  -我不...
- You did. - I don't--
我们正在增进感情时
You see, we were actually bonding
突然想起了他对你的所作所为
when I suddenly remembered what he had done to you,
我想确保
and I-- well, I wanted to make sure
没有人会再对你做那样的事
that no one ever did that to you again.
所以我问他是怎么发现
So I asked him how he found out
丹尼尔·哈德曼挪用公款的事情的
about Daniel Hardman's embezzlement,
他是这样说的
and he started with the words,
"那是两年前"
"It was two years ago."
杰夫  我可以解释
Jeff, I can explain.
你当然可以解释
You can always explain,
但那意味着你所说的
but that just means your whole story
关于路易把他名字弄上墙的办法都是瞎扯的
about how Louis got his name on the door is bullshit.
我是来跟你说实话的
And I came here to tell you the truth.
又是胡扯
More bullshit!
那我现在告诉你
Then let me tell you now.
你不懂吗  那已经过去了
Don't you get it? We're past that now.
-我不想知道了  -杰夫
- I don't want to know! - Jeff--
其实  我从不想知道  我只是
In fact, I never really wanted to know, I just--
我只是想让你告诉我实话
I just wanted you to tell me.
但现在  无论你告诉我什么
But now, no matter what you tell me,
我都不会相信是真的
I won't ever believe it's the truth.
杰夫  让我进去
Jeff, let me in.
结束了  杰西卡
It's over, Jessica.
都完了
It's done.
我们结束了
We're done.